# William G. dos Santos

San Marcos, CA 442-888-4260 willdossantosdesigns@gmail.com Hi there! I'm Will and I'm a multi-disciplined designer with over 15 years of experience. To me, design is about more than just pushing pixels on a screen. It's about creating meaningful experiences, providing clear answers, and creating sustainable storytelling that can open up doors for new opportunities.

## **Experience**



GoGoPool - The Woodlands, TX 2022 - Present

- Established Branding as Founding Designer
- Lead design, frontend, and marketing teams across bug and feature development
- Created and implemented design system foundations
- Provided in-depth illustration libraries for marketing and social media teams

#### **Lead Designer**

Planning Center - Carlsbad, CA 2011 - 2022

- Lead frontend developer for multiple products across various platforms and devices
- Conducted user experience interviews and gathered analytical feedback to create wireframes and flowcharts
- Lead design for illustration, marketing, and product teams
- Directed and edited multiple ad campaigns including high end motion graphics

#### **Lead Designer (Contract)**

ReadyFive - San Marcos, CA 2016 - 2023

- Established Branding as Founding Designer
- Lead design, frontend, and marketing teams across bug and feature developement
- Created and implemented design system foundations
- Implemented styling to streamline social media marketing

### **Education**

#### **Bachelor of Science**

Art Institute - Inland Empire, CA 2009 - 2011

- Received multiple awards including Addy and Deans List Awards for Marketing and Product Design
- Guest teaching for video, illustration, and motion graphic classes



WILLDOSSANTOS.COM